<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on “Let the Dataset Change Your Mindset”</title>
    <link>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on “Let the Dataset Change Your Mindset”</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jason.locklin.science/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Deploying a Virtual Private Shiny Server</title>
      <link>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/shinyserver/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/shinyserver/</guid>
      <description>Why Shiny and Surveydown? Link to heading Shiny is a mature product for creating dynamic web applications (typically dashboards) with R. It&amp;rsquo;s been around a while and developed professionally by Posit. Surveydown is a brand new project that uses Shiny as the engine for surveys. Keep that in mind. It&amp;rsquo;s very new and being actively developed.
Writing surveys in code opens up several valuable possibilities:
Transparency: Version controlling your survey code provides a clear history of changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R Workshops</title>
      <link>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/workshops/</guid>
      <description>I Can Help You or Your Department Use R! Link to heading R is a transformative tool in education research, combining powerful analytical capabilities with systematic transparency and reproducibility. Through nearly two decades of conducting research with R and associated tools, I&amp;rsquo;ve developed deep expertise in using these tools and I love opportunities to pass on my experience by sharing skills to help other researchers enhance their capabilities. This has evolved into delivering workshops that focus on practical, hands-on learning that I have provided for the Association of Educational Researchers of Ontario and a research team at an Ontario School Board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources Page</title>
      <link>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/resources/</guid>
      <description>Custom Search I have found that searching for technical questions has become rather difficult as ai blog mills have started filling search results with useless garbage. I suggest anyone struggling with this create their own custom &#34;programmable search engine&#34; that searches only sites they consider good sources of information on the topics they need to search. This can be done with Google here. In my own version, I have various R related community pages and blogs, plus sites like reddit and stackexchange, as well as the roots of mailing list reflectors that have their archives indexed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R Lang</title>
      <link>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/r/</guid>
      <description>As a research scientist working across public education and healthcare, I rely heavily on R for its robustness and adaptability in statistical analysis and data visualization. I started working with it in my undergraduate statistics courses twenty years ago, and I have watched it develop from relative obscurity to a powerhouse of data science and rapid data analysis. I have a deep appreciation for the developers who brought this Free tool to the world of science, and am ever eager to learn more or share what I have learned.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
