<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jason Locklin, PhD.</title>
    <link>http://jason.locklin.science/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jason Locklin, PhD.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jason.locklin.science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>R Project</title>
      <link>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/r/</guid>
      <description>R Lang Link to heading As a research scientist working across public education and healthcare, I rely heavily on R for its robustness and adaptability in statistical analysis and data visualization. I started working with it in my undergraduate statistics courses twenty years ago, and I have watched it develop from relative obscurity to a powerhouse of data science and rapid data analysis. I have a deep appreciation for the developers who brought this Free tool to the world of science, and am ever eager to learn more or share what I have learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About my work</title>
      <link>http://jason.locklin.science/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jason.locklin.science/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! I&amp;rsquo;m a community research scientist with a passion for applying extensive technical expertise to the healthcare and public education sectors. My diverse background is rooted in a blend of rigorous technical training, profound expertise in data collection, advanced statistical analysis, and a dedicated focus on data-driven decision-making and policy refinement.&#xA;At the core of my work is a commitment to equity, ensuring that student identity never predicts outcomes. In my current role as a Research Officer with the Waterloo Region District School Board (WRDSB), I&amp;rsquo;ve had the privilege of leading a variety of projects designed to assess and enhance both student and staff experiences through rigorous program evaluations and strategic planning.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
