<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>“Let the Dataset Change Your Mindset”</title>
    <link>http://jason.locklin.science/</link>
    <description>Recent content on “Let the Dataset Change Your Mindset”</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jason.locklin.science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Resources Page</title>
      <link>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/resources/</guid>
      <description>Custom Search I have found that searching for technical questions has become rather difficult as ai blog mills have started filling search results with useless garbage. I suggest anyone struggling with this create their own custom &#34;programmable search engine&#34; that searches only sites they consider good sources of information on the topics they need to search. This can be done with Google here. In my own version, I have various R related community pages and blogs, plus sites like reddit and stackexchange, as well as the roots of mailing list reflectors that have their archives indexed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R Lang</title>
      <link>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jason.locklin.science/posts/r/</guid>
      <description>As a research scientist working across public education and healthcare, I rely heavily on R for its robustness and adaptability in statistical analysis and data visualization. I started working with it in my undergraduate statistics courses twenty years ago, and I have watched it develop from relative obscurity to a powerhouse of data science and rapid data analysis. I have a deep appreciation for the developers who brought this Free tool to the world of science, and am ever eager to learn more or share what I have learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About my work</title>
      <link>http://jason.locklin.science/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://jason.locklin.science/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! I&amp;rsquo;m a community research scientist with a passion for applying technical expertise to research problems in our communities. Since completing my PhD, I have enjoyed the opportunity to do so in both the public education system and healthcare sector. My background is rooted in a blend of rigorous technical training, expertise in data collection, advanced statistical analysis, and a focus on translating that work into data-driven decision-making or policy refinement.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
